[
    {
      "question": "Quanto é 2+2?",
      "choice1": "2",
      "choice2": "4",
      "choice3": "22",
      "choice4": "17",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual o valor da soma: 17+5?",
      "choice1": "21",
      "choice2": "22",
      "choice3": "12",
      "choice4": "32",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Quanto vale 37+38?",
      "choice1": "65",
      "choice2": "68",
      "choice3": "85",
      "choice4": "75",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Quanto é 5+8?",
      "choice1": "12",
      "choice2": "10",
      "choice3": "11",
      "choice4": "7",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual o valor da soma: 17+15+7?",
      "choice1": "33",
      "choice2": "29",
      "choice3": "39",
      "choice4": "37",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Quanto é 53+69?",
      "choice1": "120",
      "choice2": "124",
      "choice3": "122",
      "choice4": "132",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Quanto vale 73+58?",
      "choice1": "131",
      "choice2": "133",
      "choice3": "121",
      "choice4": "123",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual o valor da soma: 23+36+17?",
      "choice1": "86",
      "choice2": "76",
      "choice3": "70",
      "choice4": "94",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual o valor da soma: 9+7+5?",
      "choice1": "23",
      "choice2": "27",
      "choice3": "19",
      "choice4": "21",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Qual o valor da soma: 9+14+7?",
      "choice1": "40",
      "choice2": "29",
      "choice3": "31",
      "choice4": "19",
      "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
      "answer": 5
    }
  ]
  